<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon id="skin.arctic.zephyr.martian" version="3.17.0" name="Arctic: Zephyr (martian)" provider-name="jurialmunkey, beatmasterrs, martian89">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.gui" version="5.17.0"/>
        <import addon="script.skinshortcuts" version="2.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.image.resource.select" version="3.0.0"/>
        <import addon="plugin.video.themoviedb.helper" version="5.4.16"/>
        <import addon="resource.images.weathericons.white" version="0.0.6"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.gui.skin" defaultthemename="Textures.xbt" debugging="false" effectslowdown="1">
        <res width="1920" height="1080" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="1080i" />
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>Creative Commons Attribution Non-Commercial Share-Alike 3.0</license>
        <forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=382650</forum>
        <source>https://github.com/martian89/skin.arctic.zephyr.martian</source>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot-01.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot-02.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot-03.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot-04.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot-05.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot-06.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot-07.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot-08.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot-09.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot-10.jpg</screenshot>
        </assets>
        <news>[CR][B]3.17.0[/B][CR]- Added support for videoasset containers (kodi 22)[CR]- Updated indicator icons in list views[CR]- New implementation of poster indicator icons[CR]- Fixed new content indicators for seasons and episodes[CR]- Implemented fallback for season plot labels (kodi 22)[CR]- Use decoded FilenameAndPath in info and video versions dialog (kodi 22)[CR]- Added add-on settings entry to view settings menu[CR]- Improved NextAired status for TV shows[CR]- Added games category to settings dialog[CR]- Added IMDb, RT and MC ratings in library view[CR]- Fixed layout of clock with AM/PM time[CR][CR][B]3.16.2[/B][CR]- Improved indicators to work with TMDbHelper[CR]- Cleanup of indicator settings[CR]- Small layout improvements for DialogSettings[CR]- Fixed height of plot textbox in low list[CR][CR][B]3.16.1[/B][CR]- Added support for new audio codecs[CR]- New layout of DialogSettings to support kodi 22[CR]- Updated Chinese translations (thx wabisabi926)[CR]- Added track number to music OSD and home now playing info[CR]- Added bits per sample to music OSD flag icons[CR][CR][B]3.16.0[/B][CR]- Widgets are no longer scrolling off the home screen at end of list (optional)[CR]- Improved focus handling for better usability with a mouse[CR]- Removed mouse warning[CR]- Media info flags can now be enabled for vertical menus[CR]- Automatically display studio/record label logos in info dialogs[CR]- Display clearart by default in video info dialog[CR]- Removed clearlogo and rating flag icon from info dialogs[CR]- Fixed an issue where fanart was displayed for movie sets instead of landscape[CR]- Added episode info to EPG and some PVR views[CR]- Provide rating info for PVR[CR]- Fixed various issues with override rating with user rating option[CR]- Fixed missing info labels for widgets from add-ons[CR][CR][B]3.15.6[/B][CR]- Fixed display of rating stars in music visualisation[CR][CR][B]3.15.5[/B][CR]- Fixed flickering background when leaving music visualisation[CR][CR][B]3.15.4[/B][CR]- Fixed color of stars in custom rating dialog[CR]- Fixed height of plot textbox in cleanflix home view[CR][CR][B]3.15.3[/B][CR]- Avoid unnecessary clearing of background on each redraw[CR][CR][B]3.15.2[/B][CR]- Fixed label for tvshows in widgets[CR][CR][B]3.15.1[/B][CR]- Removed deprecated views[CR][CR][B]3.15.0[/B][CR]- Changed addon id to skin.arctic.zephyr.martian[CR]- Automatically select default weather fanart from available resource addons[CR]- New screenshots for home menu and library view selection[CR]- Added missing light preview images for home menu and music view types[CR]- Use same (original) menu height for all home view types[CR]- Reflections don't change the overall home layout anymore[CR]- Changed multi widgets layout to be more compact[CR]- Changed layout of vertical menus to allow for longer labels[CR]- Fixed vertical position of icons/posters and scrollbar in all flix views[CR]- Added support for dontautoshowwidget option to modern home view[CR]- Adjusted plot textboxes height to work properly with autoscrolling[CR]- Enabled autoscrolling for plot by default[CR]- Fixed focus problem in DialogAddonInfo[CR]- Set default color scheme to dark with light dialogs[CR]- Hide multi-widgets navigation options if home menu does not use multi-widgets[CR]- Removed up-next options from skin settings[CR]- Removed option to use old view selector[CR]- Removed option to display media flags on home screen with vertical menus[CR]- Removed option to hide bottom menu[CR]- Removed option to always show vertical menu[CR]- Removed option to switch to fullscreen on music playback[CR]- Removed options to replace poster/landscape/preview with keyart/fanart/thumb[CR]- Removed clearlogo option for non netflix home view types[CR][CR][B]3.14.0[/B][CR]- Added pause on info to video OSD[CR]- Implemented bottom OSD for music with theme and reloaded options[CR]- Standard music side OSD matches current theme[CR]- Adapt title length in OSD to available space[CR]- Fixed text overflow in side OSD[CR]- Removed plot overlay from video OSD[CR]- Removed music OSD clear logo option[CR]- Removed option to disable channel logo background in PVR OSD[CR]- OSD media flags are now automatically enable/disabled by furniture setting[CR]- Changed weather window from horizontal to vertical scrolling[CR]- Simplified implementation of netflix preview window[CR][CR][B]3.13.0[/B][CR]- New design and defaults of music visualisation options for easier setup[CR]- Updated design for Modern home view to match the original AZ design[CR]- Cleanup of home menu and now playing settings[CR]- Added option to display extra fanart to skin settings[CR]- Removed global settings from view option menus[CR]- Removed dialog info settings from skin settings[CR]- Removed hide widget label option[CR]- Removed deeper shadow, focus item zoom and glow options[CR]- Added cancel button to keyboard and numeric dialogs[CR]- Added scrolling support to systeminfo window[CR]- Added missing default icons[CR]- Listed plugin.program.autocompletion as supported plugin[CR]- Renamed fallback font to DejaVu Sans[CR]- Changed Reloaded font set to use bold fonts[CR]- Fixed layout of heading on classic/featured home screen[CR]- Fixed text overflow in mediainfo list and wikipedia view[CR][CR][B]3.12.0[/B][CR]- New color scheme selection including customizable background colors[CR]- New implementation of color picker[CR]-Set default brightness of netfix preview window to 80%[CR]- Use TMDbHelper to get fanart and clearlogo for PVR[CR]- Removed support for PVR artwork addon[CR]- Improved fallback fanart in extended now playing mode[CR]- Fixed visibility of seekbar and artwork in music visualization[CR]- Enabled video lyrics by default[CR]- Use current background for plot overlay[CR]- Addon script.globalsearch is now optional[CR][CR][B]3.11.0[/B][CR]- Changed addon title and branding to Arctic: Zephyr (martian)[CR]- Updated addon dependencies[CR]- Cleanup of AZ category in SkinSettings[CR]- Removed forecast for days 6 - 11 from MyWeather[CR]- Improved handling of weather fanart as fallback[CR][CR][B]3.10.0[/B][CR]- Added new color schemes with mixed dark/light colors[CR]- Use dark with light dialogs as default color scheme[CR]- Changed the defaults of top250 and mpaa furniture flags[CR]- Reset skin settings to defaults after the user has selected reset[CR]- No longer reset shortcuts on reset of skin settings[CR]- Adjusted various labels in settings dialog[CR]- Provide fallback fanart for movies, tvshows and music[CR]- Use new default background if no fallback image is defined[CR]- Removed backup/restore from skin settings[CR]- Automatically hide netflix preview window in views when blur is enabled[CR][CR][B]3.9.0[/B][CR]- New navigation for video and music info dialogs[CR]- Added wikipedia and crew info to person info dialog[CR]- Replaced embuary info with TMDBHelper[CR]- Use TMDBHelper for fanart blur[CR]- Removed dependencies to embuary helper[CR]- Added missing conditionals to borders[CR]- Fixed plot text height in video and music info dialogs[CR]- Removed support for skin.helper.service, service.library.data.provider and script.skin.info.service[CR]- Cleanup of skin shortcuts[CR]- Fixed hubs header[CR][CR][B]3.8.0[/B][CR]- New layout for list item selected indicators[CR]- Updated VideoLyrics to V2[CR]- Fixed multiwidgets sublabel[CR]- New monochrome icons for video aspect ratio[CR][CR][B]3.7.0[/B][CR]- Open Sans is now the default font[CR]- Added RobotoNoto font with (almost) complete support for all languages supported by kodi[CR]- Updated RobotoCondensed font to latest version[CR]- New icons for HDR10 and HDR10+[CR]- Use IMDb instead of IMDB in all labels[CR][CR][B]3.6.0[/B][CR]- Added support for Open-Meteo weather plugin[CR]- Font size and layout changes in weather views/widgets[CR][CR][B]3.5.2[/B][CR]- OSD type is now a global options[CR]- Fixed toggeling of weather furniture options[CR]- Check for active weather plugin[CR][CR][B]3.5.1[/B][CR]- Use smaller fonts in vertical navigation[CR]- Fixed vertical home menu layout[CR][CR][B]3.5.0[/B][CR]- Added RobotoCJKSC font[CR]- Updated Open Sans font files[CR]- Removed Assistant font[CR]- Cleanup of font definitions[CR][CR][B]3.4.0[/B][CR]- Improved layout of media flag icons[CR]- Use global media flag icon settings for video OSD[CR]- Filled circles for video resolution/episodes count[CR]- New icons for MP2 (white), VP8, VP9 and AV1[CR]- Fixed skin settings for rating stars when media flag icons are not enabled[CR]- Fixed font color in controller setup dialog[CR]- Cleanup of icon files[CR][CR][B]3.3.0[/B][CR]- Implemented game players dialog[CR]- New PVR guide controls[CR]- Fix layout of video OSD in pause mode[CR]- Update of default font MC360[CR][CR][B]3.2.0[/B][CR]- Added new dialogs for games: SelectGameSaves, InGamesSaves, PortSettings[CR]- Redesign of controller profiles dialog[CR]- Fixed settings dialogs for game stretch, orientation and video filters[CR]- Moved game settings into separate menu[CR][CR][B]3.1.1[/B][CR]-Changed spacing between rating flags[CR]-Added extra space between rating icons and labels[CR]-Use white rating icons if "use media icons" is not active[CR]-Include IMDb rating in homescreen and white flag icons[CR][CR]3.1.0[CR]- Added video versions/extras support[CR]- Display selected state for list items even when list is not focused[CR]- Refactoring of DialogSelect.xml[CR]- Added 3D to textual video media flags[CR]- Map codec names for video media flags[CR]- Added support for SDTV/HDTV media source icons[CR]- Rely on ListItem.HdrType to detect HDR mode (except for HDR10+)[CR]- Fixed incorrect display of BluRay icon when a 3D move doesn't have .3D in it's name[CR]- Changed layout of textual video/audio media flags[CR]- Optimized layout of media flag icons[CR][CR]3.0.3[CR]- Fixed issue with tv show indicators[CR][CR]3.0.2[CR]- Added preshow experience support[CR]- Language updates[CR][CR]3.0.1[CR]- Minor adjustments[CR]- Language updates[CR][CR]3.0.0[CR]- Kodi Omega version</news>
        <summary lang="de">Klar, minimalistisch, elegant, einfach, leicht.</summary>
        <summary lang="en">Clean, minimal, elegant, simple, light.</summary>
        <summary lang="en_AU">Clean, minimal, elegant, simple, light.</summary>
        <summary lang="en_US">Clean, minimal, elegant, simple, light.</summary>
        <summary lang="es">Limpio, minimalista, elegante, simple, ligero.</summary>
        <summary lang="fr">Clair, minimaliste, élégant, simple et léger.</summary>
        <summary lang="fr_CA">Net, minimal, élégant, simple, léger.</summary>
        <summary lang="lt">Švari, minimali, elegantiška, paprasta, lengva.</summary>
        <summary lang="nl">Schoon, minimaal, elegant, simpel, licht.</summary>
        <summary lang="pl">Prosta, minimalista, elegancka i lekka.</summary>
        <summary lang="ro">Curat, minimalist, elegant, simplu, ușor.</summary>
        <summary lang="ru">Опрятный, минималистичный, элегантный, простой, светлый.</summary>
        <summary lang="zh_CN">干净，简约，优雅，简单，轻便。</summary>
        <description lang="de">Arctic: Zephyr - Martian basiert auf dem original Arctic: Zephyr Skin von jurialmunkey und dessen Erweiterungen durch beatmasterRS. Es ist ein minimalistisches, klares und simples Interface für deine Medien mit dem gewissen Etwas.</description>
        <description lang="en">Arctic: Zephyr - Martian is based on the original Arctic: Zephyr skin, created by jurialmunkey and it's extension by beatmasterRS. Arctic focuses on being simple, clean and minimalistic with a light spin.</description>
        <description lang="en_AU">Arctic: Zephyr - Martian is based on the original Arctic: Zephyr skin, created by jurialmunkey and it's extension by beatmasterRS. Arctic focuses on being simple, clean and minimalistic with a light spin.</description>
        <description lang="en_US">Arctic: Zephyr - Martian is based on the original Arctic: Zephyr skin, created by jurialmunkey and it's extension by beatmasterRS. Arctic focuses on being simple, clean and minimalistic with a light spin.</description>
        <description lang="fr">Arctic: Zephyr - Martian est basé sur le skin original Arctic: Zephyr, créé par jurialmunkey et son extension par beatmasterRS. Arctic se focalise sur le fait d&apos;être simple, claire et minimaliste.</description>
        <description lang="zh_CN">Arctic: Zephyr - Martian 是基于 jurialmunkey 所创 Arctic 皮肤的第三个版本，以及 beatmasterRS 对该皮肤的扩展版本。Arctic 系列皮肤主打简洁、干净且简约的风格，并略带独特设计巧思。</description>
    </extension>
</addon>
